University of Connecticut Libraries
© 2005 University of Connecticut
University of Connecticut Libraries, Advisory Council on Evaluation and Promotion Committee Records
1974-2005.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
University of Connecticut Libraries. Advisory Council on Evalution and Promotion Committee.
.5 linear feet.
MSS19980146
The Council was created to advise the Director of the Libraries on the evaluation and promotion of professional librarians employed by the University.
History
Created to advise the Director of the Libraries on the evaluation and promotion of professional librarians employed by the University.
Scope and Content
The collection contains chronological collection of revisions to the criteria for promotion and personal service record and reports on what is a librarian.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
Librarians—Rating of.; Library personnel management.; College librarians—United States.; Universities and colleges—Connecticut.; Job evaluations—Connecticut.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Administrative Records.
Occupations:
Committee.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Transferred to Archives & Special Collections by the outgoing chair of the committee in 1998.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Records, 1974-2005
  - Annual Meeting, 1998 Spring (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Criteria, 1974-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Criteria, 1979-1983 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Criteria, 1986-1990 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Criteria, 1993-1996 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Criteria, 1997 May (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Criteria, 1998 June (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Criteria, 1999-2000 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Criteria, 2000-2001 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Criteria, 2001-2002 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Criteria, 2002-2003 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Criteria, 2003-2004 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Criteria, 2004-2005 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - History, 1991-1992 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - PSR instructions, 1998 June (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - PSR training, 1997 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Statistics, 1974-1991 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - “Who is a Librarian?” report and correspondence, 1982-1993 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Job Classifications (Box 2)
  - Tucker Report
  - Training Tape
  - Annual Reports, 1974-1993
  - Resource Materials
  - Minimal Education Requirements
  - PSR & Criteria change
  - PSR Form
  - Promotional Process